Preliminary Inventory of the Ohio State University, Internal Audit Records, 1897-2000 RG.6.B.2
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.1989.0121, 1980-1987; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for First-Year Students of Exceptional Financial Need Report on Internal Acct and Administrative Controls & Compliance Info and Report on Financial Statements & Supplementary Info, June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for First-Year Students of Exceptional Financial Need, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Health Professions Student Loan Program, Nursing Student Loan Program, Scholarship Program for First-Year, Students of Exceptional Financial Need, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, June 30, 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Touche Ross & Company, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Letter of Recommendations on Internal Control, June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Report to Management, September 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 10)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Years ended June 30, 1984 and 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 11)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Years Ended June 30, 1983 and 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 12)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Report to Management, September 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 13)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Development Fund, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Years Ended June 30, 1982 and 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 14)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 15)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report to Management, Year Ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 16)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report to Management, Year Ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 17)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report to Management, Year Ended June 30, 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 18)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Hospitals, Report to Management, June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 19)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Hospitals, Compliance and Management Report, June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 20)
  - Management Responses to Coopers & Lybrand, undated (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 21)
  - Compliance Examination, 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 22)
  - Management Responses to Coopers & Lybrand, Compliance Examination, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 23)
  - Management Responses to Coopers & Lybrand, 1981, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Comments and Recommendations to Management, Year Ended June 30, 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 25)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, Year Ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 26)
  - Arthur Andersen & Company, The Ohio State University, Verification of Securities of the Endowment Fund, Trusts and unitrusts, Pooled Income Funds, Development Fund, Endowment Income Fund and Temporary Investments Fund, Together with Auditor's Report, as of November 20, 1981 and December 18, 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 27)
  - Linda Lucas-Miller, The Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report on Certain Direct Expenditures Charged To Federal and Non-Federal Research and Training Agreements For the Two Years Ended, June 30, 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 28)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report on the Examination of Financial Statements, Years Ended June 30, 1984 and 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 29)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report to Management, June 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 30)
  - Perms & Co. Inc., The Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report on OMB Circular A-110 Administrative Controls and Compliance Information, For the Period, July 1, 1985 - June 30, 1987 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 31)
  - Touche Ross, Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 32)
  - Touche Ross, Ohio State University Research Foundation, Report on Internal Control, Year Ended June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 33)
  - Management Report to the President, 1980-81, The Ohio State University, Office of Business and Administration, September 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 34)
  - Touche Ross, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements and Additional Information, Year Ended June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 35)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 36)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 37)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended, June 30, 1983 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 38)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 39)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 40)
  - The Ohio State University, Columbus Ohio, Entity Number 1316025986A1, National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work-Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity Grants Program, Pell Grants Program, Guaranteed Student loan Program, Report on Internal Accounting and Administrative Controls and Compliance Info and Report on Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, Year Ended June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 41)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Columbus Ohio, Entity Number 1316025986A1, National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work-Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity Grants Program, Basic Educational Opportunity Grants (Pell Grants) Program, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 42)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Columbs Ohio, Entity Number 1316025986A1, National Direct Student Loan Program, College Work-Study Program, Supplemental Educational Opportunity Grants Program, Basic Educational Opportunity Grants (Pell Grants) Program, Report on Examination of Financial Statements, Year Ended June 30, 1981 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 43)
  - Parms, Smith & Co., The Ohio State University Housing Commission, Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, Financial Statements & Supplementary Data (with accountant's report thereon), June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 44)
  - Parms, Smith & Co., The Ohio State University, Dormitory Revenue bond Funds, Financial Statements and Supplementary Data (with accountants' report thereon), June 30, 1986 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 45)
  - Parms, Smith & Co., The Ohio State University Housing Commission, Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, Financial Statements and Supplementary Data (with accountants' Report Thereon), June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 46)
  - Parms, Smith & Co., The Ohio State University Housing Commission, Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, Financial Statements and Supplementary Data (with accountants' report thereon), June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 47)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance Examination for the two years ended, June 30, 1980 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 48)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance Examination for the two years ended, June 30, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 49)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University Compliance Examination for the two years ended, June 30, 1984 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 50)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, The Ohio State University, Compliance Examination for the year ended, June 30, 1985 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 51)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, University - Industry Collaboration, Making it Work, Presentation to Dr. Edward H. Jennings, The Ohio State University, October 21, 1982 (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 52)
  - Correspondence, FY 1985, Lead File (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 53)
  - Audit Reports, FY 1985, Lead File (Box UA.1989.0121.0001, Folder 1, Item 54)
- Accession Number UA.1993.0070, 1988-1992; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  Audit reports and follow-up reviews.
  - 1988 January-June (Box UA.1993.0070.0001)
  - FY 1988 (Box UA.1993.0070.0001)
  - FY 1989 (Box UA.1993.0070.0001)
  - FY 1990 (Box UA.1993.0070.0001)
  - FY 1991-1992 (Box UA.1993.0070.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1995.0077, 1981-1988; 12.0 Cubic feet; (10) cartons
  Audits performed by Internal Auditing. Inventory lists project number, department audited, type/project, and auditor.
  - Project No. 0230: Industrial Design:Bobsled Project, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 0380: Botany: Equipment Inventory, 1987 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 0500: Humanities Administration: Management, 1988 May (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 0557: History Department: Equipment Inventory, 1988 January (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 0671: Mathematics: Petty Cash, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 0722: Economics Department: Equipment Inventory, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 0775: Political Science: Equipment, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 0766: Psychology: Equipment Review, 1987 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 0892: ATI Academics Support, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 0928: Lima Campus, 1988 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 1070: Business Research and Support Services, 1987 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 1500: School of Public Administration: Revenue, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0001, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 1127: Agronomy: Equipment, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1141: Dairy Science: Management, 1987 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1154: Farm Science Review: Management, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 1163: Horticulture Department: Equipment Inventory, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 1163-89092: Department of Horticulture: Management, 1989 March (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1173: Natural Resources: Petty Cash, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 4235: University Center for International Studies: Special(Study Tours), 1988 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0002, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 4270: National Center for Research in Vocational Education (NCRVE): Petty Cash, 1988 January (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 4505: Office of Registration Services(Transcript Office): Assets Protection, 1981 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 4506: Admissions Office: Petty Cash, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 4515: Student Organizations and Activities Office: Cash Loss, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 4700: Personnel Services(Tax Treaty), 1988 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 4710: Child Care Center: Management, 1988 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5020: University Systems: Multiple Virtual Storage(MVS), 1987 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5025: Business Management (Stores and Food Facilities): Special, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5050: Physical Facilities: EDP, 1988 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 5050: Physical Facilities: Petty Cash, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 5050-801: Physical Facilities: Fraud Audit, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0003, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 5092: Traffic and Parking: Management, 1988 April (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5118: Stores: Management, 1987 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5165: Reprographics(Lincoln Copy Center): Change Fund, 1988 January (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5165: Reprographics(Bricker Copy Center): Cash Loss, 1988 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5165: Reprographics: Special, 1986 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5165: Reprographics: Special, 1987 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5191: Transportation: Petty Cash, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5200: Residence and Dining: Cash Loss(Jones Tower), 1988 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5210: Residence and Dining Halls(North Area Management): Management, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 5414: Athletics (Marriott/Gladieux Concessions): Special, 1988 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 5414: Athletics (Ice rink): Cash Loss, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0004, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 5414: Athletics( Business Office): Mangement, 1988 January (Box UA.1995.0077.0005, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5421: Bookstores: Limited Financial, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0005, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5421: Bookstores: Notebook, Undated (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5449: Ohio Union(Bodeans Concert): Special Events, 1988 May (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5449: Ohio Union(Faculty Club): Special Review, 1988 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5453: Drake Union Food Services: Cash Loss, 1987 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5477: University Airports, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5484: Property Management: Vendor Compliance, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Butler County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Cuyahoga County: Management, 1987 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Delaware County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Fairfield County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Franklin County: Management, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Greene County: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Guernsey County: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 13)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Hamilton County: Management, 1988 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 14)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Hocking County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 15)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Holmes County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 16)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Lawrence County: Management, 1988 January (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 17)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Lorain County: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0006, Folder 18)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Madison County: Management, 1987 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Medina County: Management, 1987 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Southwest District County: Management, 1987 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Muskingum County: Management, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Van Wert County: Management, 1987 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Warren County: Management, 1986: august (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Pike County: Management, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Trumbull County: Management, 1987 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Paulding County: Management, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-South District County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Summit County: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 11)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Tuscarawas County: Special, 1987 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 12)
  - Project No. 1435: Computer and Information Science: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0007, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Tuscarawas County: Special, 1987 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Washington County: Management, 1988 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 5502: OCES-Williams County: Management, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 5600: OARDC-Directors Office: Management, 1988 May (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 5693: OARDC-Research Extension Analytical Lab: Management, 1988 May (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 1265: Health, Physical Education, and Resreation: Cash Loss, 1988 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 1400: College of Engineering-Administration: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0008, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 1452: Engineering Experiment Station: Management, 1987 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 1452: Engineering Experiment Station: Cash Loss, 1988 November (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 1900: College of Social Work: Management, 1988 October (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 2501: Medical Basic Sciences: Special, 1988 April (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 2585: Psychiatry Department: Management, 1987 July (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 2700: Optometry(Downtown Clinic): Cash Loss, 1988 August (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 2927: Vet Hospital: Cash Loss, 1987 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0009, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 3200: Library Business Office: Cash Loss, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 1)
  - Project No. 3200: University Libraries(Department of Acquistion): Accounts Payable, 1987 December (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 2)
  - Project No. 3910: Campus Planning and Equipment Inventory: Special, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 3)
  - Project No. 3930: Office of the Treasurer: Cash Management, 1987 April (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 4)
  - Project No. 3930: Fees and Deposits: Cash Count, 1987 May (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 5)
  - Project No. 3940: Office of the Controller: Special, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 6)
  - Project No. 3930: Fees and Deposits: Cash Loss, 1988 April (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 7)
  - Project No. 3930: Accounts Receivable: Change Fund, 1987 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 8)
  - Project No. 3930: Student Aid Accounting: System Review, 1988 September (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 9)
  - Project No. 3942: Account Payable:Special, 1988 June (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 10)
  - Project No. 3945: Office of the Controller(Systems Development Group): Systems, 1988 February (Box UA.1995.0077.0010, Folder 11)
- Accession Number UA.1997.0001, 1986-1990; 2.4 Cubic feet; (2) cartons
  Audit reports and working papers concerning OSU Hospitals, Beechwold, Skymed and MedOhio.
  - Project No. 6000-4902 Hospitals Physicians Management (Special), 1986 June (Box UA.1997.0001.0001, Folder 1)
  - Project No.6000-90050 Hospitals Business Office, 1990 January (Box UA.1997.0001.0001, Folder 2-5)
  - Project No.6000- Hospitals Social Work Petty Cash, 1988 December (Box UA.1997.0001.0001, Folder 6)
  - Project No.6004-91080 Beechwold Practice Survey, 1990 October (Box UA.1997.0001.0002, Folder 7-8)
  - Project No. 6003-91079 Skymed Survey, 1990 October (Box UA.1997.0001.0002, Folder 9-10)
  - Project No. 6002-89085 MedOhio Management Audit, 1989 March (Box UA.1997.0001.0002, Folder 11-15)
  - Project No. 6001- Hospital Gifts Shop Cash Loss, 1987 April (Box UA.1997.0001.0002, Folder 16)
- Accession Number UA.2000.0065, 1995-2000; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  Financial reports, corrective action plans, forms, and management letters concerning the university and the Research Foundation.
  - SF-SAC Form, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 1)
  - Circular A-133 OSU Report, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 2)
  - Circular A-133 OSURF Report, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 3)
  - OSURF Financial, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 4)
  - OSU Financial, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 5)
  - OSU Management Letter, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 6)
  - OSURF Management Letter, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 7)
  - Corrective Action Plan 98-1 and 98-2, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 8)
  - Corrective Action Plan 99-1 through 99-4, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 9)
  - Year 2000 Letter, 1999 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 10)
  - SF-SAC Form, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 11)
  - Circular A-133 OSU Report, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 12)
  - Circular A-133 OSURF Report, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 13)
  - OSURF Financial, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 14)
  - OSU Financial, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 15)
  - OSU Management Letter, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 16)
  - OSURF Management Letter, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 17)
  - Summary 97-1, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 18)
  - Corrective Action Plan 98-1 and 98-2, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 19)
  - Year 2000 Letter, 1998 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 20)
  - SF-SAC Form: Revised, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 21)
  - SF-SAC Form, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 22)
  - CIrcular A-133 OSU Report, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 23)
  - Circular A-133 OSURF Report, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 24)
  - OSURF Financial Letter, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 25)
  - OSU Management Letter, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 26)
  - OSURF Management Letter, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 27)
  - OSU Financial, 1997 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 28)
  - Circular A-133 OSU Report, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 29)
  - Circular A-133 OSURF Report, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 30)
  - OSURF Financial, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 31)
  - OSU Financial, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 32)
  - OSU Management Letter, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 33)
  - OSURF Management Letter, 1996 (Box UA.2000.0065.0001, Folder 34)